<NomaiObject xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/xen-42/outer-wilds-new-horizons/main/NewHorizons/Schemas/text_schema.xsd">
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>1</ID>
		<Text>BOBER: Turns out this purple moon is quantum. It's also made of a drug from our species named Lean, so we'll go with that name.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>2</ID>
		<ParentID>1</ParentID>
		<Text>BILLY: Bober, stop explaining what this is. We have just landed here, let's explore. And we'd better make the most of it, considering how annoying it was to get here.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>3</ID>
		<ParentID>2</ParentID>
		<Text>BOBER: Great idea.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>4</ID>
		<ParentID>3</ParentID>
		<Text>KATHERYNE: Wait, what the hell is that thing?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>5</ID>
		<ParentID>4</ParentID>
		<Text>BOBER: Holy sh... That's an engraving in the stone! It looks hexagonal...</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>6</ID>
		<ParentID>5</ParentID>
		<Text>BILLY: No shit sherlock. Assuming we read this from top-left and then right and down, like our coordinate blocks on the Vessel, this pattern reads as middle-left, bottom-left.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>7</ID>
		<ParentID>6</ParentID>
		<Text>KATHERYNE: Are we not going to question why there is a piece of a Nomain coordinate on this random moon?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>8</ID>
		<ParentID>7</ParentID>
		<Text>BOBER: No, we're not. That's not important right now. What is important is that there's an engraving of the Troll Fa-</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>9</ID>
		<ParentID>8</ParentID>
		<Text>KATHERYNE: No, no hell no! Fuck no! We are NOT going to the goddamn Troll Face planet to find another coordinate! Fuck that shit. We're gonna do something different.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>10</ID>
		<ParentID>9</ParentID>
		<Text>BILLY AND BOBER: *silence*</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>11</ID>
		<ParentID>10</ParentID>
		<Text>KATHERYNE: Okay, just listen to me for a moment. Why don't we build a space station using the abundant resources in this system?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>12</ID>
		<ParentID>11</ParentID>
		<Text>BILLY: And what purpose would the station have..?</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>13</ID>
		<ParentID>12</ParentID>
		<Text>KATHERYNE: We'd use it to "hack" the Lean, so that we can easily extract all the coordinates from it.</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>14</ID>
		<ParentID>13</ParentID>
		<Text>BILLY: That's a great idea, that would save us so much time! Let's get building!</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<TextBlock>
		<ID>15</ID>
		<ParentID>14</ParentID>
		<Text>NOTE: THE STATION IS IN A POLAR ORBIT AROUND BLUE</Text>
	</TextBlock>
	<ShipLogConditions>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LEAN_STATION_RUMOR</FactID>
			<Condition>11</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LEAN_WHER_NOMAI</FactID>
			<Condition>6</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
		<RevealFact>
			<FactID>LEAN_LANDING</FactID>
			<Condition>1</Condition>
		</RevealFact>
	</ShipLogConditions>
</NomaiObject>